本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版
好了  猴崽子们  注意了  开个会
Okay, kids, listen up. Family meeting.
-没有老妈吗  -这个嘛  我们要谈的就是你老妈
-Without mom? -Well, it's about your mom.
我们要谈谈关于她怀孕这件事
We need to talk about her pregnancy.
哦  我先说
Oh, I want to go first.
我原本以为你们只准备生我一个
I thought you guys were gonna stop after one kid.
我以为生两个
I was hoping two.
-三个  -四个
-Three. -Four.
总之
Anyway...
当你们老妈在怀孕期间不舒服时
We have reached that wonderful moment in your mother's pregnancy.
我们要让她舒服  只有当她舒服了
When she gets uncomfortable. And when your mother is uncomfortable...
-我们才能舒服  -没错
-We're uncomfortable. -Exactly.
尤其到你们老妈临盆的时候  她就会变得有点
The third trimester is when your mom gets a little...
-恐怖  -刻薄
-Scary? -Mean?
-厌恶  -恶心
-Nasty? -Icky?
所以在此阶段
So until further notice,
不管你们老妈问你什么
Whenever your mother asks you something,
你们都要回答“是”
The answer is "yes."
如果她问我是否叫拉尔夫呢
What if she asks me if my name is Ralph?
-她为什么会问你这个  -她为什么不会问我这个
-Why would she do that? -Why wouldn't she do that?
早
Morning.
-真是个美好的早晨啊  -这个颜色太配你了
-It is a good morning. -That is so your color.
-你们搞什么  -是的
-What's going on? -Yes!
-是什么  -是的
-Yes, what? -Yes!
呃  不是  我是说  不是
Er, no! I mean... no.
我叫拉尔夫
My name is Ralph!
搞什么啊
What was that all about?
哦  拉尔夫就那个样子
Oh, just Ralph being Ralph.
亲爱滴  你感觉如何啊
So how are you feeling, honey?
你看起来气色不错啊
'Cause you look terrific.
-闭嘴吧  鲍伯  -是的
-Shut up, Bob. -Yes!
嘿  查莉  地下室太乱了  吃完早餐后
Hey, Charlie, the basement is a mess. After breakfast,
-你给我下楼把你的玩具收拾好  -不
-I want you to go downstairs and pick up your toys. -No!
你再说一遍
What did you say to me?
是的
Yes!
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
■
翻译： Johnny-Z
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z  cometwang
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Your life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第三季第一集
Good Luck Charlie  S03E01  Make Room for Baby
在冒险天地里又度过了美好的一天
Another great day at super adventure land.
炎炎烈日下连演了八场  只为挣那微薄的薪水
Eight shows in the hot sun for minimum wage?
-有什么可美好的  -这是反讽  斯宾塞
-What's so great about it? -It's sarcasm, Spencer.
再给你来个  你问起来好香啊
Here's another example: You smell delightful.
你真是文采过人啊  灰臭姑娘
You're a little rank yourself, cinder-smella.
-真高兴我们又和好如初了  -是啊
-I'm so glad we're back together. -Me too.
知道我们应该如何吗
You know what we need to do?
-我们应该去表演室内戏  -对  要有空调
-We need to get into this indoor shows. -Oh, with air conditioning.
哦  我听说有个戏正在招人
Oh, I heard that there's an opening.
在爱国匹萨店  表演“乔治和马莎·华盛顿”
In patriotic Plaza to play George and Martha Washington.
-你怎么知道的  -我偷听贝琪·罗斯这么说的
-How do you know that? -I overheard Betsy Ross.
在厕所里  她和哈莉特·塔布曼一起蹲厕所呢
In the bathroom. She was in the stall next to Harriet Tubman.
他们总能知道亚伯·林肯蹲没蹲厕所
They can always tell when Abe Lincoln's in the stall.
那顶大帽子
The hat.
言归正传  扮演乔治和马莎·华盛顿的两个人
Anyways so, um, George and Martha Washington.
因为没病而请病假  被炒鱿鱼了
Were fired Because they called in sick when they weren't.
这么说来我们的国父也撒撒小谎
So the father of our country can tell a lie.
你太幽默了
That was very witty.
谢谢
Thanks.
你是不是还不懂什么叫做反讽
You're still not getting the sarcasm, are ya?
有人拿走了我的报纸
Somebody's been stealing my newspapers.
嘿  达布尼夫人  近来可好啊
Hey, Mrs. Dabney. How are you doing?
有人拿走了我的报纸
Somebody's been stealing my newspapers.
你怎么还看报纸
You still get the paper?
如今大多数人都会在英特网上看新闻
Nowadays most people get their news on the Internet.
英特什么
The inter what?
英特网
The Internet.
不知道吗  就是信息高速路
You know, the information super-highway.
别跟我说鸟语
Stop talking gibberish.
我的报纸呢
Where is my newspaper?
我们没拿你的报纸
We don't have your newspaper.
好了  快做完学校作业
All right, almost done with my school proj...
嘿  达布尼夫人
Hey, Mrs. Dabney.
我早就应该想到你就是那个偷报纸的贼
I should have known you were the newspaper thief.
别冤枉人  偷报纸的不止我一个人
No, I'm not the only guilty one here.
这个需要合作才能完成
It was a two-man job.
好了  谁想要体育
Okay, who wants the sports sec...
嘿  达布尼夫人
Hey, Mrs. dabney.
再跟我说说英特网
Tell me more about this Internet.
鲍伯  咱们要谈谈了
Bob, we've gotta talk.
你的子民偷我的报纸  该如何处置
You people stole my paper. What are you gonna to do about it?
-搬家  -双手赞成
-We need to move. -Works for me.
拿着
Here you go.
-什么东西  -房地产代理的名片
-What's this? -It's the business card of a real estate Agent.
自从盖比出生后  我就一直把它带在身上
I've been carrying that around since Gabe was born.
我就知道会有这一天的
I knew this sweet day would come.
老天开眼啊
Hallelujah!
这个也一直带在身上
Been carrying that around too.
呃  亲爱的
Um, honey,
我们为什么要搬家
why do we have to move?
我刚才去后院  看见有坨猫屎在草坪上
I went in the backyard. There was cat poop on the lawn.
-我去收拾行李了  -别急
-I'll start packin'. -Hold on.
我们要搬家就是因为一些猫
We're have to move because some cats.
-在咱们的草坪上方便  -哦  让我说完
-Did his business on the lawn? -Oh, let me finish.
听着  那只猫让我想到了  如果某天我们养只宠物
Okay, the cat made me think that it would be nice.
那该多好啊
To have a pet someday.
然后我又想到  我们没地方养宠物了
And then I thought, we don't have room for a pet!
我又意识到咱们的小宝宝也没有地方啊
And then I realized we don't have room for a baby.
我是说  不管是他还是她  都应该有自己的房间啊
I mean, he or she should have their own room, right?
打断一下  我没整明白  我们是要搬家还是要养宠物
Excuse me, I'm not clear... are we moving or getting a pet?
我们需要个新家  你觉着呢  老鲍
We need a new house. What do you think, Bob?
呃  这个  我们
Um, well, we...
嘿  爸  你早先是怎么跟我们说的
Hey, dad, what was that thing you were telling us earlier?
当老妈问我们问题时  我们应该说
When mom asks us a question we say...?
我一会再收拾你
I will deal with you later.
不是  不是  说的不是这个
No no, it wasn't that.
亲爱的  听着  我理解你的感受
Honey, look, I understand your feelings.
我们确实需要更大的空间  跟你说吧  我来操办
We do need more room. You know what? I'm on it.
-好样的  -如果我们选择养宠物
-Good boy. -If we are going down the pet road,
能养只猴子吗
Could we get a monkey?
因为我有顶牛仔帽
'Cause I have this little cowboy hat.
可从来不知道该怎么搭配
That I have never known what to do with.
我们可以排练下试镜吗  华盛顿先生
Shall we rehearse for our audition, Mr. Washington?
来吧  华盛顿夫人
Hit it, Mrs. Washington.
很久以前  在战争胜利之后
Many years ago, after the war was won...
-我们需要个领袖  -华盛顿怎么样啊
-We needed a leader. -How 'bout Washington?
他就是那个
He was just the man.
带领自己的祖国前进的人
To take his country farther.
-而他背后的女人  -就是他的贤妻马莎
-And the woman behind him... -Was his loving wife Martha.
你去向何方啊  华盛顿将军
Where are you going, general George?
我要去福吉谷打仗
I'm off to fight at valley forge.
但我先要带领他们横渡这片水域
But first I'll lead them 'cross the water.
那就是二十五美分图案的由来
That's what put him on the quarter!
别了  我的夫君  我会想念你的微笑的
So long, my dear, I'll miss your smile.
给  不如让它温存片刻
Here, why don't you keep it awhile?
-我们是华盛顿夫妇  -华盛顿夫妇
-We're the washingtons. -The washingtons.
华盛  华盛  华盛  华盛顿夫妇
The washa washa washa washingtons!.
直走  直走  左转  左转
And straight and straight and left and left.
好了  睁开眼睛吧
And okay, open your eyes.
-哦  -嗒哒
-Ooh. -Ta-dah!
什么东西
What is it?
-婴儿房啊  -你喜欢吗  老妈
-It's the new baby's room! -Do you love it, mom?
我们将近花了一个小时呢
We spent almost an hour on it.
这么说来  小宝宝要睡在
So the baby will be sleeping.
楼梯下面
Under the stairs.
就像哈利·波特
Like Harry Potter?
嘿
Hey,
哈利·波特  他的经历可不平凡啊
Harry Potter, now he had some fun adventures, huh?
是吧  说点关于哈利·波特的好话
Huh? Say something good about Harry Potter.
魁地奇
Quiddich!
亲爱的  听着
Honey, look...
我跟你说  看好了  看看把小宝宝
You know what? Look, how easy it's gonna be.
抱出婴儿床有多容易
To pull the baby out of the crib, huh?
易如反掌
Almost too easy!
现实中是不会出现这种状况的
That would never happen in real life.
现在发生了  以后还会再次发生
You've dropped 'em before, you'll drop 'em again.
嘿  老妈  瞧瞧这个
Hey, mom, check this out.
如果小宝宝又哭又闹  想让这个小家伙安静下来
If the baby gets fussy, calm the little munchkin.
就让他看看大海
With an ocean view.
嘿
Hey!
新房子  老鲍  晓得吗
New house, Bob. Got it?
呃哦  有鲨鱼
Uh-oh. Shark!
-什么东西  -所有你往我家
-What's all this? -Everything you've ever.
扔过来的  发射过来的  烧毁的东西
Thrown, shot or fired into my house.
哦  乖乖  你太让我失望了
Oh... boy, you were a disappointment.
你怎么把这些东西都还回来了
Why are you giving all this stuff back?
盖比  如今你要搬走了  我就在想啊
Gabe, now that you're moving away, I've been thinking:
虽然你也我硝烟四起
You and I have had our differences,
但事实上  你让我的生活变得丰富多彩
but the truth is you've made my life more interesting.
你让我永葆青春
You've kept me young.
看来我失职了
I haven't done a very good job.
我会非常怀念你的这种幽默感的
There's that sense of humor I'll miss so much.
嘿  我超喜欢的棒球帽
Hey, it's my favorite baseball cap.
还记得当你丢了它的时候吗
Remember when you lost that?
记得  我想往你的花坛中扔颗臭气弹
Yeah, I was trying to plant a stink bomb in your flower bed.
实话跟您说吧  达布尼夫人  这么多年以来
You know, Mrs. Dabney, after all these years,
这是我们首次享受这美好的一刻
that's the first nice moment we've ever shared.
慢走 不送
Bye, now.
同志们  我们来这干嘛  到底是什么惊喜
Guys, what are we doing here? What's the big surprise?
这是你的新家
This is your new house!
-什么  -我们真的要搬家了
-What? -We're really moving?
但是我喜欢以前的老房子
But I love our old house.
你会更喜欢这个新房子的
You'll like the new house even more.
-至少我们应该商量下啊  -不是刚商量过吗
-Can't we at least talk about this? -We just did.
-我们已经把老房子卖了吗  -还没
-So we sold our old house already? -Nope!
还留着呢
Still own that one.
通常你会先卖掉老房子
Normally you sell the old house first.
但如今我们有两栋房子  好耶
But now we own two houses. Yay.
在新房子里  大家每个人都有自己的屋子
And in this house, everyone gets their own room.
我终于摆脱地下室了吗
Do I finally get out of the basement?
那还用说
You sure do.
呃  你的卧室在
Uh, here your bedroom is on...
地下一层
Level b-1!
呃  老天
Ugh, man,
这里有点热啊
It's kinda hot in here.
你们干吗都盯着我
Why are you all staring at me?
我的帽子里怎么都是头发
Why is my cap full of hair?
我知道怎么来的
I know where your cap got it.
啊
Ahh!
达布尼
Dabney!
我来搞定
I got him.
查莉  你喜欢这个新家吗
Charlie, you like your new home, don't you?
不  妈咪
No, mommy!
查莉
Charlie!
你有什么事吗
Is something on your mind?
或者我应该说  你没有什么事吗
Or should I say <i>not</i> on your mind?
你往我的帽子里抹脱发剂
You put hair removal goo in my cap!
这是偷我报纸的代价
That was for stealing my newspapers.
亮点是  我在网上查到的整人点子
And the funny part is I got the idea on the Internet.
这事没完
This isn't over.
哦  此言差矣
Oh, but I think it is.
你灰溜溜的搬走了  我笑到了最后
You're moving away and I get the last laugh.
哈  哈  哈
Ha ha ha!
妄想  你不会笑到最后的
No, you're not gonna get the last laugh!
我才是笑到最后的人  而且笑起来应该是这样
I'm getting the last laugh! And it's gonna sound like this:
-哈  哈  哈  -哈  哈  哈
-Ha ha ha ha! -Ha ha ha ha!
-Ha ha ha! -Ha ha ha!
哈
Ha!
我们之间的关系错综复杂
We have a complicated relationship.
嗨  我刚收到你的短信
Hi. I just got your text.
-你搬家了  -是啊
-You're moving? -Yeah.
要搬家了  我有点难过
We are. I'm kinda sad about it.
我会怀念这个地方的
I'm gonna miss this place.
呃  听着
Um, well,
还有些坏消息
Here's some more bad news.
冒险天地打电话了
Super adventure land called...
哦  我们落选了
Oh, and we didn't get it?
其实  是你落选了
Actually, <i>you</i> didn't get it.
你被选中了  哦  你会告诉他们
But you did? Oh, but did you tell them.
没有我  你是不会接戏的
That you weren't gonna do the show without me?
这个  我是想这么说
Well, I was gonna,
但是下个星期肯定酷暑难耐  所以
But it's supposed to be really hot next week, so...
哦太好了  我还要继续亲臭汗青蛙
Oh great. So I'm stuck kissing a sweaty frog.
-差不多吧  -那现在是谁演马莎·华盛顿
-Pretty much, yeah. -So who's playing Martha Washington?
-珊迪·修普  -谁
-Sandy Super. -Who?
米尔顿·修普的侄女  冒险天地的创始人
Milt Super's niece. You know, the guy who founded super adventure land.
等等  是珊迪·修普
Wait, is Sandy Super.
那个老盯着你看的可爱女生
That really cute girl who's always staring at you.
还老约你出去  无视我的存在
And asking you out and pretending I don't exist?
-看来你知道她  -哦
-So you do know her. -Oh.
好吧  也许新青蛙也是个帅哥
Well, maybe the new frog will be really cute too.
事实上
Actually,
他们把这个角色给了操控旋转椅的家伙
They're giving that part to the guy who runs the tilt-a-whirl.
格瑞西·乔
Greasy Joe?
-恐怕是的  -难道没有牙
-Afraid so. -Don't you have to have teeth.
-也可以演青蛙吗  -恐怕是的
-To play a frog? -Afraid not.
两份房租
Two house payments.
嘿  老爸
Hey, dad,
我能
Can I...
喔  你眼睛怎么了
Whoa. What's going on with you eye?
你老妈的主意
Your mother has ideas.
价值千金的主意
Expensive ideas.
没关系  我对着另一只眼睛说
That's okay. I'll just look at the other eye.
好了  老爸  问个问题
So, dad, quick question,
你觉着挖个坑需要多长时间
How long do you think it would take to dig a pit?
-多大的坑  -呃  不清楚
-How big a pit? -Eh, I don't know.
和达布尼夫人的长宽高差不多吧
About as tall and as wide as Mrs. dabney.
盖比  你又要整什么
Gabe, what are you up to?
-你很想知道吗  -花我的银子吗
-How much do you want to know? -Is it gonna cost me any money?
-不  -挖去吧
-No. -Happy digging.
你去向何方啊  乔治将军
Where are you going, general George?
我要去福吉谷打仗
I'm off to fight at valley forge.
但我首先要带领他们横渡这片水域
But first I'll lead them 'cross the water.
带上我吧  我想你应该会的
Take me too, I think you oughter.
-泰迪  -谁是泰迪
-Teddy? -Who's Teddy?
我是本·富兰克林
I'm Ben Franklin.
呃  你来作甚  本
Uh, what are you doing here, Ben?
是啊  戏里没你啊
Yeah, you're not in this show.
她是说历史中的这一段
She means this part of history.
哦  乔治啊  乔治
Oh, George, George,
大家都知道你没去福吉谷
Everyone knows you didn't go to valley forge.
拯救我们的国家
To save our country.
你去那里是因为你和马莎
You went because you and Martha.
出现了问题
Were having problems.
-什么  -于是你投靠了好朋友
-What? -So you turned to your best friend,
本·富兰克林  那个一直默默支持你的人
Ben Franklin, who's always been there for you.
-不  他没有  -有  他有的
-No, he didn't. -Oh yes, he did.
后来托马斯·杰斐逊安慰了马莎
Then Martha was comforted by Thomas Jefferson,
剧中将由格瑞西·乔扮演
played in this performance by greasy Joe.
哦  乔
Oh Joe!
乔
Joe!
别吃玉米热狗了  快过来
Quit gummin' on that corndog and get out here!
美国就是这样起步的
And that's how America got started.
-拜托了  查莉  -不
-C'mon, Charlie. -No!
-怎么了  -我们遇到状况了
-What's going on in here? -We've got a situation.
某人不愿意收拾行李
Someone is refusing to pack.
哦  查莉宝贝  你需要打包一下你的玩具
Oh, Charlie honey, you have to pack your toys
这样我们才能去新家玩啊
So we can take them to the new house.
不  我不走
No! I'm staying!
是啊  其实我也想留下来
Yeah, actually I kinda want to stay here too.
PJ  你别捣乱
P.J., you're not helping.
但是我有很多美好的回忆在这栋房子里
But I have so many great memories at this house.
比如  我把脑袋卡在了秋千架上
Like, when I got my head stuck in the swing set.
乖儿子  在新家里有很多地方
Honey, you're gonna get your head stuck.
可以任你将脑袋卡住
In lots of places at the new house.
说话算话
Promise?
真希望这次再生个闺女
I really Hope this one's another girl.
好了  查莉  怎么才能让你
Okay, Charlie, what's it gonna take.
今天就搬去新家啊
To get you in a new house today?
-小马  -好的
-Pony. -Done.
老鲍
Bob!
嘿  里面怎么回事
Hey, what just happened in there?
这个嘛  我觉着我们知道了
Well, I think we found out.
珊迪不善于即兴表演
That Sandy's no good at improv.
泰迪  你是嫉妒珊迪·修普吗
Teddy, are you really jealous of Sandy Super?
没有  我为什么要嫉妒
No, why would I be jealous.
一个可爱  聪明
Of somebody who's cute and smart.
有钱的人
And rich?
听着  泰迪  你不用担心
Look, Teddy, you have nothing to worry about.
在这个世界上  我只愿意跟你在一起
There's no one in the world who I'd rather be with than you.
-真的  -真的
-Really? -Really.
乔治·华盛顿
George Washington,
你是我这辈子最好的男朋友
You're the best boyfriend I've ever had.
你也同样是我这辈子最好的女朋友  本·富兰克林
And you're the best girlfriend I ever had, Ben Franklin.
哦  把脸凑过来
Oh, come here.
我让你尝尝过电的滋味
I'm gonna teach you something about electricity.
哦  来吧
Oh yeah.
好了  查莉  就这样了
Well, Charlie, this is it:
这是我们在埃奇伍德的最后时光了
Our last few moments on edgewood drive.
我会怀念这个地方的
I gotta say I'm gonna miss this place.
成了  泰迪  走吧
Come on, Teddy, let's go.
一会再剪掉
I'll edit that out later.
好了  咱们新家再见
Well, see you at the new house.
好运了  查莉
Good luck, Charlie.
好了
Okay.
我突然想到了什么  我马上回来
You know what? I'll be right out.
感觉忘拿什么东西了
I feel like I forgot something.
欢迎回家  PJ
Welcome home, P.J.
这就是你要慢慢长大的地方
This is where you're going to grow up.
-不  -嘿  嘿
-No-ooo! -Hey hey.
我们就生两个  对吧
We are stopping at two, right?
这个嘛  其实
Well, actually...
哦  不会吧
Aw no.
盖比真老实
Gabe is such an easy baby.
真希望一直如此啊
I Hope he'll always be like this.
“所有的小鸭子都找到了回家的路
"Then all the little ducklings found their way home.
从此过上了幸福快乐的生活”
And lived happily ever after."
谢谢
Thank you.
亲爱的  找到什么了吗
Honey, find what you were looking for?
找到了
I did.
我们不搬了  老鲍
We can't move, Bob.
什么
What?
我抱着四个孩子都走过了那扇门
I carried all four kids through that door.
我想抱着第五个孩子也同样走过那扇门
I want to do the same with number five.
怎么了
What's going on?
我们不搬了
We're not moving.
我们不搬了  嘿  嘿  卸车
We're not moving! Hey hey, unpack the truck!
真的吗  太好了
Are you kidding? That's awesome.
我们哪也不去了
We're staying right here.
就在自己的家里
In our home.
快点  大家  快离开这里
Come on, people, let's get out of here!
我们不搬了  老妈改主意了
We're not moving. Mom changed her mind.
什么
What?!
不  不  不  我们必须走  马上
No no no, we have to go! Right now!
喔  喔  喔
Whoa whoa whoa.
你又捅什么娄子了
What did you do?
-什么娄子也没捅  -救命啊
-I didn't do anything. -<i>Help!</i>
无视之
Ignore that.
怎么了
What's going on?
这个小恶魔在我的门廊上涂满了胶水
That little monster covered my entire porch with glue.
信件上也是
Even the mail.
-盖比  你这是为何啊  -我要笑到最后
-Gabe, why did you do that? -I had to get the last laugh.
好吧  但是这并不可笑
Okay, but that's not funny.
有点可笑
It's kinda funny.
-倒是帮把手啊  -好的  坚持住  达布尼夫人
-A little help here. -Okay, hang on, Mrs. dabney.
-我们来救你  -我来吧
-We'll get you unstuck. -I got it.
-呃  -等
-Uh... -Wai...
我来不了了
I don't got it.
好了  查莉  我们又变成一户人了
Well, Charlie, we're back to being a one-house family.
一家人
A one-home family.
把我们美翻了
And we couldn't be happier.
一会再剪掉
I'll edit that out later.
哦  对了  斯宾塞和我被
Oh, so Spencer and I were fired.
冒险天地炒鱿鱼了
From super adventure land.
很显然  本·富兰克林
Apparently, Ben Franklin.
亲乔治·华盛顿被认为
Kissing George Washington was deemed.
有悖历史
Historically inaccurate.
尽管他们很喜欢对方
Although they did like each other...
相当的喜欢
A lot.
嘿  大家
Hey, guys,
PJ又把脑袋卡在秋千架上了
PJ got his head stuck in the swing set again.
好的  我去拿工具
Okay. I'll get my tools.
我去拿黄油
I'll get the butter.
家的感觉真好
There's no place like home.
好运喽  查莉
Good luck, Charlie.
很久以前  冒险天地的
<i>Many years ago,</i> <i>the founders</i>
创始人聚集在一起  开了一次意义非凡的会议
<i>of super adventure land</i> <i>gathered for a very</i> <i>important meeting.</i>
先生们  我们建造了这座主题公园
Gentlemen, we've built this beautiful theme park,
现在就差个名字了
Now all we need is a name.
我想到个  我们就叫它天地的冒险超级乐园
I know. We'll call it land of adventure super.
就知道你会把自己的名字放在前面  理查德·天地
Of course you'd put your name first, Richard land.
那好吧  你有何建议  弗兰克·冒险
Well then, what do you suggest, Frank adventure?
名字脱口而出
Something that rolls right off the tongue.
“冒险的超级天地乐园”
"Adventure of super land."
不错哦
That's not bad.
不错  让我做点修改
Not bad. Let me make one slight adjustment.
我们就叫它“超级天地的冒险乐园”
We'll call it: "Super land of adventure."
先生们
Gentlemen.
噩耗啊  我们刚收到电报
Terrible news! We've just got this telegram.
亚瑟·的
Arthur Of...
去世了
Is dead.
的是死的了
Of's been offed?
恐怕是
I'm afraid so.
亚瑟·的死了  就剩咱们仨了
With Arthur Of gone, it's down to just the three of us:
超级  冒险  天地
Super, adventure, land.
贝蒂  泡壶咖啡  我们要讨论一阵子
Betty, put on a pot of coffee. We're gonna be here awhile.